https://kenjigohyiqian.myportfolio.com/work https://www.linkedin.com/in/gohyiqian kenji.gohyiqian@gmail.com +65 9129 5608

An objective-driven and design-sensitive software developer with a total of 4.5 years' working experience in web application development, project management and 3D computational design. Passionate to build meaningful products, my past work experiences gave me an edge in communicating with designers and stakeholders. I design all the UI of my App before building them!

SKILLS

FRONTEND

ReactJS, Redux, Bootstrap, Tailwind CSS, Styled components, CSS Flexbox

BACKEND

Node, Express, MongoDB, PostgreSQL. Django Rest Framework

UX & UI & DESIGN

Adobe Photoshop, Illustrator, XD, Premier Pro, Figma, Sketching

CRM Solutions

Salesforce Platform and Marketing Cloud

3D Modelling

Rhino3D, Revit Building Information Modelling, Grasshopper Scripting

Physical Prototyping

3D Printing, 3D Scanning, Laser Cutting, Robotic Arm Thermoforming

EDUCATION

<u>General Assembly (GA)</u> <u>Software Engineering Immersive</u>

June 2021 - Dec 2021

<u>Singapore University of Technology & Design (SUTD)</u>

- BSc in Sustainable Design
- Master in Architecture with Distinction GPA: 4.5/5.0
- Material Research
- 2D-to-3D Parametric Form-Finding
- Python Programming

May 2012 - Aug 2016

Meridian Junior College

Bio, Chem, Math, Economics

2008 - 2009 (UAS:86.25/90)

ACHIEVEMENTS

- Shortlisted to Participate in DBS Hack2Hire Hackathon (Oct 2021)
- Best CumInCAD Research Paper Award 2017 on Robotic Arm Thermoforming: http://papers.cumincad.org/cgibin/works/Show?caadria2017 005
- **SUTD Merit Scholarship** for BSc and Master Degree (2012 -2016)
- Summit 6050m Mountain in Indian Himalayan (Now Mt. SUTD)
- ZJU Asian Leadership Program (2013)
- Honorable Mention for Perfect GPA in SUTD Senior Year 2012
- MJC Academic Excellence Award for A'Level (2009)

PROJECTS

GarageSale

E-commerce Marketplace with Admin, Sellers, Shops and Buyers, seamlessly integrated with PayPal payment gateway

- **Front End:** ReactJS, Redux, React-bootstrap, styled components and tailwind CSS are used for styling and animations.
- **Backend:** Django Rest Framework, PostgreSQL, Image storage on Amazon S3 via S3Boto3Storage.
- **Deployment:** https://mygaragesale.herokuapp.com/

Watch Demo on Youtube:

https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=G58NseSpyYc&t=1s

CryptoTrader

A Crypto Trading app with user wallet and buy/sell function. Live crypto token prices are fetched using CoinGecko API.

- Front End: ReactJS, React-bootstrap
- Backend: ExpressJS, NodeJS, MongoDB
- **Deployment:** https://mycryptotrader.herokuapp.com/

Watch Demo on Youtube:

https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=1qQJP-07RSA&t=6s

DiyLifeStyle

A meal planning app that allows user to customize their own meal and monitor their calories intake and take charge of their lifestyle.

- Front End: CSS, Bootstrap
- Backend: ExpressJS, NodeJS, MongoDB, PassportJS
- **Deployment:** https://diylifestyle.herokuapp.com/

Watch Demo on Youtube:

https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=5miVKELN33k&t=51s

WORK EXPERIENCE

Full Stack Developer | Ailytics | Present

• React, Django, Typescript, Microsoft VoTT, ElectronJS, Snap.svg

Salesforce-NTU Kickstarter Program Trainee | June - Dec 2021

• Salesforce CRM System, Marketing Cloud and Tableau Data Analytics

Project Manager | People's Association | Jan 2020 - Jul 2021

- Manage project timeline, secure funding and control budget for projects averaging \$15 mil
- Planning and design of new and upgrading community club projects to meet objectives and guidelines.
- Led the project teams of Architects and Engineers on assigned projects, conduct monthly updates to stakeholders

Architectural Executive | DP Architects | Oct 2017 - Dec 2019

• Concept Design, Project Management, Coordinate Client Meetings

Architectural Designer | Spark Architects | Jul 2016 - Aug 2017

• Concept Design, Product Design, 3D Modelling, 3D Printing

CERTIFICATIONS

React Certification | HackerRank | Oct 2021

https://www.hackerrank.com/certificates/59fac0e618c6

Google Agile Project Management | Coursera | May 2021 coursera.org/verify/VRJKQMSDV3KD

coursera.org/verity/vkJkQM3DV3kD

IBM Data Science Professional Certificate | Coursera | Aug 2019 coursera.org/verify/specialization/NFYVTPSC89PQ